[
  {
    "id": "T6B01",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Which is true about forward voltage drop in a diode?",
    "answers": [
      "It is lower in some diode types than in others",
      "It is proportional to peak inverse voltage",
      "It indicates that the diode is defective",
      "It has no impact on the voltage delivered to the load"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6B02",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What electronic component allows current to flow in only one direction?",
    "answers": [
      "Resistor",
      "Fuse",
      "Diode",
      "Driven element"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6B03",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which of these components can be used as an electronic switch?",
    "answers": [
      "Varistor",
      "Potentiometer",
      "Transistor",
      "Thermistor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6B04",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following components can consist of three regions of semiconductor material?",
    "answers": [
      "Alternator",
      "Transistor",
      "Triode",
      "Pentagrid converter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6B05",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What type of transistor has a gate, drain, and source?",
    "answers": [
      "Varistor",
      "Field-effect",
      "Tesla-effect",
      "Bipolar junction"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6B06",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "How is the cathode lead of a semiconductor diode often marked on the package?",
    "answers": [
      "With the word \"cathode\"",
      "With a stripe",
      "With the letter C",
      "With the letter K"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6B07",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What causes a light-emitting diode (LED) to emit light?",
    "answers": [
      "Forward current",
      "Reverse current",
      "Capacitively-coupled RF signal",
      "Inductively-coupled RF signal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6B08",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What does the abbreviation FET stand for?",
    "answers": [
      "Frequency Emission Transmitter",
      "Fast Electron Transistor",
      "Free Electron Transmitter",
      "Field Effect Transistor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6B09",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What are the names for the electrodes of a diode?",
    "answers": [
      "Plus and minus",
      "Source and drain",
      "Anode and cathode",
      "Gate and base"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6B10",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following can provide power gain?",
    "answers": [
      "Transformer",
      "Transistor",
      "Reactor",
      "Resistor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6B11",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What is the term that describes a device's ability to amplify a signal?",
    "answers": [
      "Gain",
      "Forward resistance",
      "Forward voltage drop",
      "On resistance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T6B12",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What are the names of the electrodes of a bipolar junction transistor?",
    "answers": [
      "Signal, bias, power",
      "Emitter, base, collector",
      "Input, output, supply",
      "Pole one, pole two, output"
    ]
  }
]